Assume the position.
Secretary is a romance, drama, comedy film directed by Steven Shainberg.
A young woman, recently released from a mental hospital, gets a job as a secretary to a demanding
lawyer, where their employer-employee relationship turns into a sexual, sadomasochistic one.
Mr. Grey, played by James Spader.
Lee Holloway, played by Maggie Gyllenhaal.
Peter, played by Jeremy Davies.
Joan Holloway, played by Lesley Ann Warren.
Burt Holloway, played by Stephen McHattie.
Dr. Twardon, played by Patrick Bauchau.
Secretary is a 2002 American erotic romantic comedy-drama film directed by Steven Shainberg from a screenplay
by Erin Cressida Wilson, based on the 1988 short story of the same name by Mary Gaitskill.
Starring Maggie Gyllenhaal and James Spader, the film explores the intense relationship between a dominant lawyer and his
submissive secretary, who indulge in various types of BDSM activities such as erotic spanking and petplay.
The film explores themes of suicide, clerk, fetish, sadomasochism, secretary.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.